Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Andries Coetzee.
I'm coming from South Africa.
This is my fiancée Jacqueline.
This is our baby boy Ethan Coetzee.
The thing that brought me to The SCOAN was addiction to drugs, cigarettes and drinking.
I smoked for 22 years and drank for 22 years.
In between that, I used drugs as a habit.
In the morning, afternoon and when I wanted to go to bed, I wanted to do drugs.
I used abusive words on my fiancée.
I met her three and a half years ago and things were not good with us.
I never wanted to go to church; I never wanted to talk to God or talk to anybody.
I just wanted to be by myself and do my work.
I would be aggressive to work colleagues, especially the ones who were closest to me.
I had done it for twenty-two years and eight months.
I have bruises and marks all over my body that I can show you
because I was drinking and acting aggressively.
At what age did you start smoking, drinking alcohol?
Since the age of 16 or 15.
It has been for how many years now?
That is about 23 years exactly.
You said you had some scars on your body.
Can you show us and tell us these scars came about?
This is caused by alcohol aggression.
I would get annoyed and would just want to fight for no reason.
I was just like the devil was at the back of my mind telling me, “You have to do this”.
This one was caused by drinking beer.
This one was caused by smoking weed.
This one took more than 17 stitches and it was also caused by drugs I was using.
This one on my leg was from two years ago.
I got annoyed in the house.
I wanted to make trouble with me fiancée.
I took my clothes out of the drawer and started tearing them with a knife.
It was bad and I started abusing her.
What happened, how did you get that injury?
I stepped on the pants and wanted to cut them with a knife.
The knife didn’t go through the pants; it went straight to my leg.
It was after taking alcohol?
It was after taking alcohol.
You say you smoked cigarettes and what?
Weed.
Each time you smoked...
How did it make you feel?
How did that affect your life generally?
It affected the ones close to me most – the annoyance, abuse, fighting and bad temper.
It affected them and it affected me in a bad way.
How did the miracle happen?
My fiancée has a friend in Ghana whom we called.
One day I said to my fiancée, “Please can you ask your friend for one package from The SCOAN?”
So, my fiancée spoke to her.
How did you get to know about The SCOAN?
I started watching.
We have DSTV so I changed the channel and saw Emmanuel TV.
I saw Prophet T.B. Joshua praying and I saw all these great testimonies and people being healed.
I said I wanted to give my life to God
because the way I was living was not the way of God; it was the way of the devil.
Did you, at any time, try to stop these dangerous habits: smoking, taking weeds and alcohol?
Yes, I made more than seven attempts but there was absolutely nothing, none at all.
When you saw the Emmanuel TV, what happened?
When I saw Emmanuel TV, I saw all these great testimonies coming from people.
I saw people getting healed and delivered.
That was when I started talking to my fiancée, telling her I needed to change my life
because my life was going in a wrong direction.
After asking her friend to get the Morning Water package for us,
we got it on a Tuesday and we started to pray and anoint ourselves.
We went on our knees and I said, “God of Prophet T.B. Joshua, if You are there,
please, listen to me, help me and answer my prayers as I do not want to be the same person”.
So, you have never been here before?
Never.
Wow.
You requested the package of the Morning Water and after praying with it, the miracle happened.
Tell us how this addiction finally stopped.
On Tuesday we got it, we started praying and using it.
We went on our knees and I started reading the Bible.
I said, “Please, God of Prophet T.B. Joshua, please listen to my prayers, please answer my prayers.
I know You are annoyed with me because of the wrong doings in my life
but I know I can change my life around because with You, all things are possible”.
Nothing is impossible so I said to my fiancée that it is better we use the Morning Water.
Wow, we can see the emotional expression there.
We all believe this is born out of great joy, of a deliverance from a bondage of so many years.
So, after the prayer...?
After the prayer, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, I started feeling itching on my body.
We took the CD of Prophet T.B. Joshua where he was prophesying.
We put it in and started listening to the words.
We went on our knees and touched the TV and I and my fiancée said,
“Please, God of Prophet T.B. Joshua, turn our lives around
because it is only You who can do it for us; nobody else can do it”.
Only God can do good things in your life because you cannot do any good thing.
I started to itch badly.
For more than thirty to forty minutes, I started to itch all over my body.
I said to my fiancée, “I’m not feeling well. There is something wrong; I don’t know what’s going on”.
We went to the room.
I took off all my clothes and put on new clothes; I thought it was my clothes.
I said, “No, something is really wrong”.
I put on the new clothes but I was still itching.
I went to the back of the door and started scratching my back
because my back was itching and all over was itching.
After forty-five minutes of itching, I went on my knees and started to pray.
I said, “God, please tell me what is happening because I do not know what is happening with myself".
I have some photos my fiancée took when it was happening.
After the itching, what happened?
That is the best part of everything.
After the itching, I went down on my knees and prayed.
After praying, I went to the porch – I usually smoked and drank on the porch.
I went and sat on the porch.
I took the cigarette and as soon as I lit it and put it in my mouth,
I said, “Something is not tasting well” and I threw the cigarette down.
It has been more than two months now that I have not touched beer!
I do not touch alcohol, cigarettes or drugs!
Nothing!
Hallelujah!
Glory be to God!
You have some pictures to show us there.
We would like you to explain what we can see on those pictures.
This was just after watching the CD when I stared scratching.
I had scratches on the back and the front.
This is one of the photos.
The other one - if you can turn...
You didn't understand what was itching all over your body?
Nothing at all.
The moment the itching stopped - you mean that was the end of urge to smoke and drink?
That was the end of everything.
Really, there was no taste for cigarettes.
I didn’t look at beer; I didn’t want to drink it.
I just want to tell God, “Thank You!”
Shall we clap for Jesus Christ!
Can we hear a word or two from your fiancée?
My name is Jacqueline.
I'm from Liberia.
This is my fiancé and this is my little baby boy.
My fiancé has already explained it all.
Since I met him three years ago, he had been smoking a lot.
He could smoke three to four packets of cigarettes a day.
Sometimes, I would really get annoyed with him and would say,
“Please leave the cigarettes; they are not good for you and they are not good for your health”.
He would say, “Oh, leave me”.
Sometimes, even if we didn’t have money,
we would borrow cigarettes from the nearest shop just for him to smoke.
It was really bothering me but I just gave all to God, for God to take control.
Last year in November, we were watching Emmanuel TV.
I had been seeing a lot of testimonies and the goodness of God through this ministry.
So I told him that we should always watch Emmanuel TV.
Every night and every morning, we watch Emmanuel TV and then we pray along with Prophet T.B. Joshua.
One day, I called my friend and I said it would be better if we got the Morning Water package
because through the Morning Water, I had seen a lot of people get their deliverance.
I believed that we would have our deliverance, too.
I asked one of my friends in Ghana and she helped.
She came here and got one Morning Water package for us.
She sent it to us and as God would have it, we got it.
It was on a Tuesday we started ministering the Morning Water.
I ministered it on him first and then I ministered it on myself and on our baby.
We started praying just like that.
Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday and on Friday we watched the CD.
As we were watching the CD, we put our hands on the screen.
Then, I just saw my fiancé scratch his body for thirty to forty-five minutes.
I asked him what was going on.
He said he didn’t know and was even confused.
I said, “OK, let’s go into the room” because we had guests in the house.
I said, “Let’s go into the room and I will minister the Morning Water on you”.
We went into the room and took all his clothes off.
He said, “Maybe the clothes are doing this; maybe they weren’t washed well”.
I said, “I don’t think so; I think it’s your deliverance”.
He took off his clothes and I started spraying.
I said, “You demon, be flushed out, in the name of Jesus!
You demon, wherever you are, you do not belong in this body!
Be flushed out, in the name of Jesus!”
And then we started praying.
I said, “God of Prophet T.B. Joshua, I know this is our deliverance, in Jesus’ name!”
I started spraying; that was how he came to himself and then we prayed.
And since then...?
Since then, he stopped taking cigarettes.
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus!
Andries Coetzee & Family
Morning Water Testimony
The next day, my baby fell sick.
His stomach started running so we took him to the hospital.
The Morning Sticker – I put it in my baby’s clothes.
His stomach was running and he was vomiting.
He was helpless.
They admitted him and the next morning, as God would have it, he was healed.
I told my husband and he said we should go to South Africa.
I said no, we have to come to Nigeria.
This is our first time here.
We had to come and testify to the goodness of God.
Hallelujah!
Put your hand together for Jesus Christ!
Thank you very much.
Lastly, can we hear a word of advice from you?
I would advise people around the world that have addictions to cigarettes, drugs and alcohol
to change your life to God because only God can deliver you from this evil.
Because it is evil; it is a spirit that is not supposed to be in your body.
Brother, turn yourself to God because God can do wonders.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Glory be to God!
We also want to encourage you, now that Jesus Christ has proven His power in your life, -
it is not enough to come to Jesus to receive help and spiritual healing...
The man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua says that when we are healed, blessed or delivered,
we must follow Jesus Christ, who is the Healer, the blessing Provider,
and make His Word the standard for our lives, so that whatever we receive from Him
will be permanent, and even will multiply, in Jesus' name!
We pray God will give you enough grace to make the Word of God a standard for your life and your family,
in Jesus' name!
Amen.
Once again, let's put our hands together for Jesus!